

CONTACT

Sai Paradise, Punawale, Maharashtra, Pune – 411033

P: 9673973040

E: kolhe.nilesh@rocketmail.com

L: https://linkedin.com/nilesh-kolhe/

G: https://nilesh-kolhe.github.io/My/#/home

SKILLS



CERTIFICATIONS

MS AZ-900

Microsoft Certified Azure Fundamentals

NILESH KOLHE

Software Developer

A Full Stack Developer with 8+ Years of Extensive Experience in Software Development and Exceptional Communication Skill, Seeking a Position Where I can use My Skills to the Advantage of the Company while Having the Scope to Develop My Own Skills.

EDUCATION

STES's Smt. Kashibai Navale College of Engineering, Pune

2010 - 2014

Bachelor of Engineering [Computer]

WORK EXPERIENCE

Atos

Consultant

2021-

Working as a Frontend Developer for application development for healthcare domain. Major work is in ReactJS as the frontend framework. MS Azure as the API.

Capgemini Technology Services

Consultant

2020-2021

Worked as a Full Stack Developer to develop applications for Finance domain. Worked on Frontend technologies of Angular 8 and its migration to higher versions. Backend tech stack mainly included Dot Net Core 3.1 Web API.

Emerson Innovation Center-Pune

Senior Engineer I

2020-2020

Worked as a Full Stack Developer to Develop applications for Finance domain. Mainly into ReactJS and Dot Net Core as the Tech Stack.

Tieto India Private Limited

Software Engineer

2017-2020

Worked as a Full Stack Developer for developing applications for healthcare domain.

Front end frameworks used were AngularJS, Angular 2+. Other Frontend technologies included HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and HighCharts.

Backend technologies included C# Web API. Testing of the C# code (Unit, Integration) as well as Frontend code by Jasmine and Karma.

Infosys Limited

Senior Systems Engineer

2015-2017

Worked on enhancement, maintenance and support of Dot Net based applications for Retail domain.